hello happy Labor Day it is day 16 of my
videos 100 and today since it's Labor
Day I was going to talk about well labor
movement and how we celebrate today due
to how hard unions fought to get a
supporting our work week a two-day
weekend and a safe work environment and
to me the next step is definitely
freeing us from labor altogether to not
have to tie our time and labor to
whether or not we can live so if we're
not forced to work 40 hours a week
or even 10 hours a week in order to put
food on the table and a roof over your
head then what do you do what do you
spend your time doing and my whole life
maybe not my whole life since I've been
about 18 19 so half my life I've been
obsessed that's wrong word I've been
learning and very intrigued with this
idea of passive income I don't know how
much I even really agree with it anymore
to get money from interest and because
any money you're getting from passive
incomes from other people can do mean
labor for you and I mean it's also from
your idea I mean there's other ways
together for sure but this idea that I
wanted to get passive income so I
wouldn't be tying my time to how much
money I had because it loses joy for me
when I get paid for something I want to
not have I want to have time freedom and
money freedom right now I have time
freedom but I definitely don't have
money freedom because careful what you
wish for
I got passive income in the form of a
disability and disability payments so I
don't have to work in order to put a
foot over my head and food on the table
and the money I do I can make a little
bit of money that is extra so and I'm
working to get off of it altogether
because I do know there's just too many
rules and so there isn't that freedom
and
since not having to work I've been able
I'm able to slash had to just sit and
think and that's how I've come up with
my purpose on this planet how I've
discovered the solution to the
everything the solution everything is
what I was able to when given time and
space and not having to the stress of
having to work and what happens if it
goes and what happens if your standard
of living is decreased in and how do I
pay my debts and how do i when it
evaporates when the universe takes it
away from you there's pros and cons but
one of the big pros is having that space
to find and so for this Labor Day when
I'm meditating cuz imma get meditated
today and I can't really control what I
want to be thinking about I believe
whatever thoughts are my head but I'm
definitely been thinking about this idea
of the labor movement and I mean I read
I'm just a different cookie oh my god
I don't know raisin oatmeal cookie in a
chocolate chip case or something or the
opposite and they you know I'm just
going off there's my child interrupting
which is what happened in the last video
cuz it's Labor Day she's home figuring
out what to do with your time is
stressful to people when they don't have
to work but when we have everyone with
that freedom to be released from stress
I do believe that we will have amazing
art and inventions and systems created
because although stress can be a
motivator it has been up to this point
in capitalism that not having food on
the table is a great motivator to get
out there and figure out what to do to
put it on the table but I don't think
it's our highest purpose I don't think
it's our highest Colleen and even if it
is even if people are driven by money
and if every if I'm the only person on
this planet that isn't driven by money
they're still high like you no one's
driven by money it's what money can buy
it's the freedom it's the materialism
it's what it can buy
and I think we can give people most of
what they want and all of what they need
for every person every of the 7 billion
people on this planet we can do that for
everyone if we cooperate and come
together and we just need the systems in
place to be able to do that because it's
easy to say hey there's like come
together big hug big hands across the
world but unless we there's a feasible
way to do that I get that that just
sounds like a pipe dream but I have a
feasible way of damina and I'm working
on I finally figure out my outline well
falling asleep last night I almost got
up writing down a way this is simple
enough I feel like I can just remember
it it was pretty much like why we need
it all of the problems that we we have
in capitalism in society now I don't
need to go there I mean I've read dozens
and dozens of books on those subjects so
like a chapter a few chapters on what
climate change is doing what poverty is
doing then a how the solution that I see
so why the global cooperative what the
global cooperative is and then the next
section is like how it works and already
that's part of it too how it works and
then what we can do with it it would be
the final section there might be three
specific sections but I I liked that and
that idea to float nicely in my brain
last night but after five minutes down
it's Labor Day and I'm gonna go and hang
out with my kid so happy Labor Day
everybody